RG 003, Litchfield County, County Court Files
Connecticut State Library
- Files, 1751-1855
  - 1817 (Box 233)
    - Garnsey-Hockox (Box 237)
    - Hide-Johnston (Box 238)
    - Johnston-Lockwood (Box 239)
    - Lord-Northrop (Box 240)
    - Northrop-Russell (Box 241)
    - Russell-Stoddard (Box 242)
    - Stone-Yale (Box 243)
  - 1818
    - Abernethy-Chittenden (Box 244)
    - Chittenden-DeForest (Box 245)
    - Deforest-Haydon (Box 246)
    - Hazen-Lamb (Box 247)
    - Lamb-Noble (Box 248)
    - Norfolk-Seymour (Box 249)
    - Seymour-Wilcox (Box 250)
    - Williams-Youngs (Box 251, Folder 1-2)
  - 1819 (Box 251)
    - Abbott-Bradley (Box 251, Folder 3-20)
    - Bradley-Cook (Box 252)
    - Cook-Guild (Box 253)
    - Gunn-Johnston (Box 254)
    - Johnston-Lyman (Box 255)
    - Lyman-Peters (Box 256)
    - Pettibone-Smith (Box 257)
    - Soule-Warner (Box 258)
    - Warner-Yale (Box 259, Folder 1-10)
  - 1820 (Box 259)
    - Abernethy-Benham (Box 259, Folder 11-20)
    - Benjamin-Cowles (Box 260)
    - Crane-Harrison (Box 261)
    - Harrison-Lamson (Box 262)
    - Landon-Mitchell (Box 263)
    - Moore-Seymour (Box 264)
    - Seymour-Wadsworth (Box 265)
    - Wadsworth-Youlen (Box 266, Folder 1-15)
  - 1821 (Box 266)
    - Abernethy-Beers (Box 266, Folder 16-20)
    - Bellamy-Goshen (Box 267)
    - Granger-Merrell (Box 268)
    - Merrell-State (Box 269)
    - Steele-Wordin (Box 270, Folder 1-15)
  - 1822 (Box 270)
    - Abernethy-Bradley (Box 270, Folder 16-20)
    - Bragg-McMahon (Box 271)
    - Tucker-Woodward (Box 273, Folder 1-6)
  - 1823 (Box 273)
    - Adam-Fuller (Box 273, Folder 7-20)
    - Galpin-Shelton (Box 274)
    - Shepard-Younglove (Box 275, Folder 1-11)
  - 1824 (Box 275)
    - Abernethy-Clark (Box 275, Folder 12-20)
    - Cole-Peck (Box 276)
    - Peet-Young (Box 277, Folder 1-17)
  - 1825 (Box 277)
    - Adam-Bloss (Box 277, Folder 18-20)
    - Boardman-Litchfield (Box 278)
    - Lockwood-Winegar (Box 279)
    - Winegar-Younglove (Box 280, Folder 1)
  - 1826 (Box 280)
    - Abernethy-Hitchcock (Box 280, Folder 2-20)
    - Hoadley-Smith (Box 281)
    - Smith-Young (Box 282, Folder 1-13)
  - 1827 (Box 282)
    - Abernethy-Case (Box 282, Folder 14-20)
    - Catlin-Mygatt (Box 283)
    - New Hartford-Titus (Box 284)
    - Tobey-Yale (Box 285, Folder 1-7)
  - 1828 (Box 285)
    - Abbott-Dorr (Box 285, Folder 8-20)
    - Downs-Smith (Box 286)
    - Smith-Yale (Box 287, Folder 1-4)
  - 1829 (Box 287)
    - Abernethy-Butler (Box 287, Folder 15-20)
    - Camp-Monson (Box 288)
    - Morehouse-Strong (Box 289)
    - Stuart-Yale (Box 290, Folder 1-8)
  - 1830 (Box 290)
    - Abbott-Cook (Box 290, Folder 9-20)
    - Cornish-Lyman (Box 291)
    - McIntire-State (Box 292)
    - Sterling-Youngs (Box 293, Folder 1-9)
  - 1831 (Box 293)
    - Abbe-Clement (Box 293, Folder 10-20)
    - Colebrook-Pelton (Box 294)
    - Pendleton-Watson (Box 295)
    - Wells-Woodruff (Box 296, Folder 1-3)
  - 1832 (Box 296)
    - Abbe-Gregory (Box 296, Folder 4-20)
    - Harrison-State (Box 297)
    - State-Woodbury (Box 298, Folder 1-9)
  - 1833 (Box 298)
    - Abbe-Catlin (Box 298, Folder 10-20)
    - Chaffee-Landon (Box 299)
    - Langdon-State (Box 300)
    - State-Yale (Box 301, Folder 1-15)
  - 1834 (Box 301)
    - Abbe-Boardman (Box 301, Folder 16-20)
    - Boardman-Humphrey (Box 302)
    - Humphrey-Stanley (Box 303)
    - State-Young (Box 304, Folder 1-13)
  - 1835 (Box 304)
    - Abbe-Bierce (Box 304, Folder 14-20)
    - Birge-Marsh (Box 305)
    - Merriam-Tuttle (Box 306)
    - Tyler-Yale (Box 307, Folder 1-6)
  - 1836 (Box 307)
    - Abbe-Gaoler (Box 307, Folder 7-20)
    - Gleason-State (Box 308)
    - State-Wright (Box 309)
  - 1837
    - Abbe-Hunt (Box 310)
    - Ives-Turner (Box 311)
    - Van Dusen-Young (Box 312, Folder 1-4)
  - 1838 (Box 312)
    - Adam-Fuller (Box 312, Folder 5-20)
    - Gaoler-Rowley (Box 313)
    - Sage-Wright (Box 314)
  - 1839
    - Abernethy-Lyman (Box 315)
    - Markham-Vincent (Box 316)
    - Wade-Winegar (Box 317, Folder 1-2)
  - 1840 (Box 317)
    - Abbe-Green (Box 317, Folder 3-20)
    - Hallock-Rowley (Box 318)
    - Sage-Wyth (Box 319, Folder 1-16)
  - 1841 (Box 319)
    - Abbe-Bellamy (Box 319, Folder 17-20)
    - Benedict-Mygatt (Box 320)
    - Newell-Sullivan (Box 321)
    - Talmadge-Wright (Box 322, Folder 1-6)
  - 1842 (Box 322)
    - Adams-Judd (Box 322, Folder 7-20)
    - Kellogg-Woodruff (Box 323)
  - 1843
    - Abbe-Sperry (Box 324)
    - State-Wyant (Box 325, Folder 1-12)
  - 1844 (Box 325)
    - Agard-Lyman (Box 325, Folder 13-20)
    - McGregor-Woodward (Box 326)
  - 1845
    - Abel-Sperry (Box 327)
    - State-Wright (Box 328, Folder 1-8)
  - 1846 (Box 328)
    - Abbott-Hyde (Box 328, Folder 9-20)
    - Jackson-State (Box 329)
    - State-Winchester (Box 330, Folder 1-9)
  - 1847 (Box 330)
    - Abernathy-Griswold (Box 330, Folder 10-20)
    - Hard-State (Box 331)
    - Stoddard-Woodruff (Box 332)
  - 1848
    - Ames-Sharon (Box 333)
    - Shelton-Young (Box 334, Folder 1-19)
  - 1849 (Box 334)
    - Alvord-Baker (Box 334, Folder 20)
    - Baldwin-Sharon (Box 335)
    - Skilton-Wright (Box 336)
  - 1850
    - Adams-Perry (Box 337)
    - Pettibone-State (Box 338)
    - State-Worthy (Box 339, Folder 1-5)
  - 1851 (Box 339)
    - Adams-Riley (Box 339, Folder 6-20)
    - Roberts-Wright (Box 340)
  - 1852
    - Abernethy-State (Box 341)
    - State-Woodbury (Box 342, Folder 1-12)
  - 1853 (Box 342)
    - Adam-Dayton (Box 342, Folder 13-20)
    - Demars-State (Box 343)
    - State-Woodworth (Box 344, Folder 1-16)
  - 1854 (Box 344)
    - Alvord-Bushnell (Box 344, Folder 17-20)
    - Canfield-State (Box 345)
    - State-Wright (Box 346, Folder 1-4)
  - 1855 (Box 346)
    - Averill-Woodruff (Box 346, Folder 5-10)
  - Discontinuances, 1831-1855
    - Adams-Merwin (Box 347)
    - Merwin-Yale (Box 348)